export const dataArray = [
    {
        question: 'What is HTML', 
        answers: {
            a: 'HyperText Markup Language',
            b: 'HyperText Makeup Link',
            c: 'HorrorTechnology Markup Language',
            d: 'Hyper Textlink Markup Language '
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a'
    }, 
    {
        question: 'What is the meaning of UI UX Design ?', 
        answers: {
            a: 'User Interface and Use Experience',
            b: 'User Introface and User Experience',
            c: 'User Interface and User Experience',
            d: 'User Interfacing and User Experience'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is Logo', 
        answers: {
            a: 'HyperText Markup Language',
            b: 'HyperText Makeup Link',
            c: 'HorrorTechnology Markup Language',
            d: 'Hyper Textlink Markup Language '
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a'
    }, 
    {
        question: 'What is the meaning of UI UX Design ?', 
        answers: {
            a: 'User Interface and Use Experience',
            b: 'User Introface and User Experience',
            c: 'User Interface and User Experience',
            d: 'User Interfacing and User Experience'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is HTML', 
        answers: {
            a: 'HyperText Markup Language',
            b: 'HyperText Makeup Link',
            c: 'HorrorTechnology Markup Language',
            d: 'Hyper Textlink Markup Language '
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a'
    }, 
    {
        question: 'What is the meaning of UI UX Design ?', 
        answers: {
            a: 'User Interface and Use Experience',
            b: 'User Introface and User Experience',
            c: 'User Interface and User Experience',
            d: 'User Interfacing and User Experience'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is HTML', 
        answers: {
            a: 'HyperText Markup Language',
            b: 'HyperText Makeup Link',
            c: 'HorrorTechnology Markup Language',
            d: 'Hyper Textlink Markup Language '
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a'
    }, 
    {
        question: 'What is the meaning of UI UX Design ?', 
        answers: {
            a: 'User Interface and Use Experience',
            b: 'User Introface and User Experience',
            c: 'User Interface and User Experience',
            d: 'User Interfacing and User Experience'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is HTML', 
        answers: {
            a: 'HyperText Markup Language',
            b: 'HyperText Makeup Link',
            c: 'HorrorTechnology Markup Language',
            d: 'Hyper Textlink Markup Language '
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a'
    }, 
    {
        question: 'What is the meaning of UI UX Design ?', 
        answers: {
            a: 'User Interface and Use Experience',
            b: 'User Introface and User Experience',
            c: 'User Interface and User Experience',
            d: 'User Interfacing and User Experience'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    }
]